http://www.maximumawesome.com/about/legal/privacy-policy

Maximum AwesomeVomiting action figures, highly questionable relationship advice, and the ever feared Blog Thunderdome.
About
First time here?
Just to say hi
Ask ‘Quite Frankly’
Privacy policy
1. Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information.
Thank you for visiting MaximumAwesome.com, Misfitopia.com, McAwesome.com, McAwesomeUniversity.com, CrapOrNotCrap.com, DaveMcAwesome.com and BlogThunderdome.com, which are humor, satire, entertainment and social networking services allowing users to communicate online with other users. These websites and services are hereafter referred to as the “Site”. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information.
Our online information collection and use practices may differ from our practices regarding information obtained offline.
Remember if you register with the Site, participate in a survey, purchase something through the website, request a catalog or enter any of our contests or promotions, you agree to these terms. As we update and expand our services, this policy might change, so check it out from time to time.
2. The Information We Collect.
At the Site you can do a variety of things. You may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in surveys, vote in polls. The types of personally identifiable information (i.e. information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) that may be collected at these pages includes: name, address, age, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. You can view or change your information at any time.
Sometimes you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card, and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to a friend, you might submit the friend’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient’s name, address, age, date of birth, gender, e-mail address and telephone number.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online or Earthlink).
3. How We Use and Disclose the Information.
We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you order a catalog, we will send to you a catalog in the mail or, if you have won a contest, sending to you an email notification that you have won. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services we offer. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, we may send to you in the mail special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please email us.
4. How We Protect Your Information.
Personal Information. Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.
Content. The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Site, such as message board postings, fan submissions, images and comments, may be accessed by other users, including people who you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.
5. How We Share Your Personal Information.
We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); and/or (d) with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the site).
Your #1 source for vomiting robot dinosaurs. Since 2005.
First time here?
Ask ‘Quite Frankly’
Just to say hi
I want to write for you
PR people
Advertising
Subscribe to our news feed. Return to top of pageCopyright © 2020 · Quattro Child Theme on Genesis Framework · WordPress · Log in
